cqzg.com 2012-06-21

# Chowcow.Com - Privacy Policy

###  Welcome

Welcome to the Chowcow.com Privacy Policy page.

###  Summary

Our Privacy Policy explains how we use personal information submitted by you through our website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Chowcow.com website. It does not apply to any third party websites that you may visit through a link you find on Chowcow.com. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy during the account creation process, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on May 25, 2010.

**Data Capture**

You can browse Chowcow.com and view listings without providing us with any of your personal information. If you choose to become a Registered User, the personal information you provide us will be stored on our servers located in the United States. By becoming a Registered Member of our website, you hereby consent to the storage of such information.

**The Information We Collect**

  1. Your first and last name, your physical address (should you choose to provide it), your email address, your gender and your age (should you choose to provide them).
  2. If you sign up for one of our paid services (i.e. Job Listings), we may also store your financial information, including your credit card number and billing address.
  3. We may also collect transactional information based on your activities which may include your posts and listings, content, and feedback.
  4. We collect information from your interaction with Chowcow.com, use of our services, and your response to content and advertising.
  5. We further gather browser and connection information, page view stats, inbound and outbound traffic stats, IP addresses and standard web log information;

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

We collect personal information primarily to protect your safety and the safety of others using our website. In an effort to prevent fraud and scams, we want to make sure that our Registered Users are not anonymous to us. In addition, we use your information to continually improve Chowcow.com and the quality of the services we provide you.

You hereby concent to our use of your personal information to:

  1. Provide you with the support and services you request.
  2. Protect your safety and the safety of others usinc Chowcow.com.
  3. Prevent fraud, scams, and to respolve disputes.
  4. Prevent prohibited and illegal activities and uphold the law.
  5. Enforce our Terms of Use and Intellectual Property Policies.
  6. Improve our services, content, and advertising.
  7. Inform you about our services, sister companies, and updates to our services.
  8. Offer you occassional promos and discounts (if you have authorized use to do so); and
  9. Comply with laws and regulations.

###  Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information when required by law, to enforce our terms of use and policies, respond to claims of fraud or scams, to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. If required, your information will only be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

**Other Uses of Your Information**

We may also use your personal information in the following manners:

  1. Provide such information to service providers that assist us with the operation of Chowcow.com for purposes such as collections, fraud investigation, and compliance with regulations and laws.
  2. Law enforcement, regulatory agencies, or other government agencies in response to court orders, subpoenas, or similar legal obligation, pretaining to criminal investigations, illegal activity, or civil matters. We will only share your information with government agencies when required to do so by one of the aforementioned methods, unless we, in our sole and absolute discretion, feel that the disclosure of your information is necessary to prevent harm or financial loss to anyone or to report suspected illegal activity conducted by you.
  3. Entities or organizations that we may merge with or that may acquire our business.

###  No Solicitation 

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for solicitation purposes without your written consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and website performance. 

**Public Information**

Your User Name on Chowcow.com is public information. Your User Name is displayed on all of your listings and throughout the website. As such, if you use your real name as your User Name, anyone who knows your real name will be able to track your listings and activities on Chowcow.com. We recommend that you do not use your real name for your User Name. 

When creating a listing, any information you put in the "Listing Details" section of your ad is public information. As such, if you choose to put your contact phone number or email address, such information will become accessible by anyone using or visiting Chowcow.com. 

If you choose to place any personal information in the "Listing Details" section, you hereby agree to release Chowcow.com, including our officers, agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and employees harmless for any misuse or abuse of such information. 

Our system has an internal communication tool that is automatically added to every listing and activated by clicking on the "Contact Lister" link on top of each ad. Users who wish to contact you can use this system to email you without ever seeing your email address. When you respond to them, however, your email address WILL be visible to them and they will be able to contact out outside of the Chowcow.com system. 

**No Tolerance Policy**  

Chowcow.com has a strict No Tolerance Policy for Spam and Spoofing. If you spam or spoof using Chowcow.com, your account will immediately be terminated without notice to you. You are strictly prohibited from adding Users, even those who have made purchases from you, to your physical or digital mailing lists without the prior written approval of that User.  If you are a Chowcow.com user and another user is sending you Spam or Spoofing, you should immediately report such user by sending an email to [spam@chowcow.com](mailto:spam@chowcow.com?subject=Spam%20Issue%20Report).

**Account Security and Your Password**

You must protect your Password at all times. Anyone who has access to your password, has complete access to your account and personal information. We strongly recommend that you carefully choose your Password using a combination of upper and lower case letters and numbers. 

We advise you not to share your Password with anyone. If you do share your Password with third parties, you hereby agree that you are fully responsible for any and all actions taken by such person(s) using your account. Granting third parties access to your Password gives them the ability to access, change, use, misuse, or abuse your information or commit fraud, which may subject you to liability and legal issues. 

If at anytime your Password becomes jeopardized, or you think it may have been jeopardized, please notify us by emailing [security@chowcow.com](mailto:security@chowcow.com?subject=Security%20Issue%20Report) and change your Password immediately. 

**Modifying or Deleting Your Account**

For security reasons, Chowcow.com cannot modify your personal information for you. If you want to modify your personal (account) information, you must log in to your account, click on "Edit Profile," and make the changes yourself. 

You are required to keep your personal and contact information current at all times. Chowcow.com may send you occasional emails to make sure that your contact information is current. 

If you wish to delete your account with Chowcow.com, you may do so by sending our Membership Department an email to [membership@chowcow.com](mailto:membership@chowcow.com?subject=Membership%20Inquiry). Within a reasonable timeframe, we will remove your account from our viewable system but will retain your personal information solely for legal compliance reasons and to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, collect unpaid balances, and enforce our Terms of Use and legal rights. 

**Disclaimer**

We go to great lengths to protect your private information. We use security tools and take all the necessary steps to insure that your information is not jeopardized. However, third parties may be able to unlawfully access our servers and your information by using criminal tactics to hack into our system. As such, by using Chowcow.com, you indicate that you understand and agree that we do not promise that your private information will never be jeopardized.
